<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hail Science Trivia</title>
    <link>/TriviaStats/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hail Science Trivia</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/TriviaStats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>00 - roboAlex</title>
      <link>/TriviaStats/2021-5-17-roboalex_1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/TriviaStats/2021-5-17-roboalex_1.0/</guid>
      <description>roboAlex 1.0 roboAlex 1.0 is simple. He knows three things: how well human Alex does on a typical round, whether or not human Alex jokered the current trivia round (this one is cheating a bit), and how well everyone else did on the current trivia round. I wish I only had to know three things.
Below I’ll go into more detail about how each of these factors contribute to the overall score.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>01 - Joker Stats</title>
      <link>/TriviaStats/2020-09-09-jokers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/TriviaStats/2020-09-09-jokers/</guid>
      <description>First, load the trivia_stats.R source file, which contains all functions for generating statistics:
source(&amp;quot;trivia_stats.R&amp;quot;) Joker Table This chart takes into account both the creators’s average round difficulty and your own bias toward or against that creator to given you an overall sense of how much better than average you tend to do on rounds made by that creator (and therefore, who you should pick to joker today).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>02 - Other Trivia Plots</title>
      <link>/TriviaStats/2020-08-18-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/TriviaStats/2020-08-18-stats/</guid>
      <description>First, load the trivia_stats.R source file, which contains all functions for generating statistics:
source(&amp;quot;trivia_stats.R&amp;quot;) Player Similarity Table This chart measures how similar players scores are on a given round (after adjusting for round difficulty). Basically - bias chart measures how well a player does on another player’s rounds, similarity table measures how similarly they perform on all the rest of the rounds.
player_similarity_table()  {&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>03 - Notes and Ideas</title>
      <link>/TriviaStats/ideas/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/TriviaStats/ideas/</guid>
      <description>Ideas Get rounds labeled and do stuff (bias table/plot for round types maybe)
do score prediction based on difficulty, player average, and round label/maybe biases
 To Do Finish player plots
Format output so we don’t have to scroll through dozens of charts to find the right one
Whose nights get Jokered most, how often was it the correct choice to joker their rounds
Clustering similar players using the covariance/similarity matrix</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>